{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957535118","data":{"timestamp":" 946957535118"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957535341","data":{"timestamp":" 946957535341"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957536305","data":{"timestamp":" 946957536304"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957537577","data":{"timestamp":" 946957537577"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957540423","data":{"timestamp":" 946957540423"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957541266","data":{"timestamp":" 946957541266"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957541579","data":{"timestamp":" 946957541578"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957542811","data":{"timestamp":" 946957542811"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957546301","data":{"timestamp":" 946957546300"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957547284","data":{"timestamp":" 946957547284"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957547538","data":{"timestamp":" 946957547537"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957548481","data":{"timestamp":" 946957548481"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957551302","data":{"timestamp":" 946957551301"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957552334","data":{"timestamp":" 946957552334"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957552807","data":{"timestamp":" 946957552807"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957557321","data":{"timestamp":" 946957557321"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957557407","data":{"timestamp":" 946957557407"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000104_064523"," gameId":" 8f309222-d46e-4d01-9ea7-eecd78357011"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}